fill me in.  how can i eavesdrop
I belong to a natgas discussion group on the internet
This is from one of the guys
Basically they are a bunch of gastraders from various firms 
a lot of producers 
some industrials
I found the test to be mildly amusing
And since I had no idea what 'club no minors' was
i was hoping for some insight from you guys
Fortunately
thelovely Ms. Shipos was able to fill me in

0.3396226

fill me in.  how can i eavesdrop?
I belong to a natgas discussion group on the internet. This is from one of
the guys. Basically they are a bunch of gastraders from various firms ( a lot
of producers, some industrials, some small shops and few i--banker types) I
found the test to be mildly amusing. And since I had no idea what 'club no
minors' was-- i was hoping for some insight from you guys. Fortunately, the
lovely Ms. Shipos was able to fill me in.